https://www.simpson-associates.co.uk/privacy-policy

All Sectors
Higher EducationHousing AssociationsBlue LightsManufacturingMedia and PublishingLegalLocal / Regional GovernmentHousebuildersTechnologyTravel & TourismHospitality
Clients
People
Team
Jobs
Events
All Events
Resources
Contact
All Sectors
Higher EducationHousing AssociationsBlue LightsManufacturingMedia and PublishingLegalLocal / Regional GovernmentHousebuildersTechnologyTravel & TourismHospitality
Clients
People
Team
Jobs
Events
All Events
Resources
Contact
Privacy Policy
By reading and continuing to use the site you agree to the following conditions of use. This website is a service operated by Simpson Associates, Regency House, York Business Park, Poppleton, York, North Yorkshire, YO26 6RW.
As you may be aware, the law changed regarding Data Protection at the end of May 2018 – the new EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) came into effect. In order to comply with the requirement of this law we have updated our Data Protection Policy.
We recognise the need to protect the personal information that we might gather from our customers, potential customers and visitors to our website. We will only use the information that we collect lawfully, in accordance with GDPR.
Information we may collect from you:
If you contact us, we will keep a record of your personal information that you provide to us.
Details of your visit to our website
If you apply for a job with us
Legitimate interests
Simpson Associates has a legitimate interest to collect personal data for the groups above. For groups 1 and 2, the data collected is limited to names, job titles, company addresses, telephone numbers and corporate email addresses. Only relevant companies are contacted who may be interested in legitimate business services that we offer. We have carried out a legitimate interests assessment, the results of which are available on request. With regards to Job Applicants, please read our GDPR Privacy Notice for Job Applicants.
Your Consent & Cookies
By accessing our website you are giving us consent to collect your personal information. The site uses cookies or similar technology to collect information about your access to the site. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site, to ensure the content of our website is useful and appropriate.
Cookies are small files that we transfer to your device, via our web browser, that enable us to remember certain information. We use cookies both to track visitor behaviour and to store site preferences. By using our website, you agree that we can place different types of cookies on your device. You can disable cookies in your browser. We use cookies to improve our website’s user experience and to measure and report on marketing performance.
Third-party cookies: In the course of serving advertisements to this website, our third-party ad servers (including Google) may place or recognise a unique cookie on your browser. User interaction with ads and ad-views across the Google Display Network and/or other display advertising networks are reported in conjunction with activity on this site. Information about your visit to this website, such as number of times you have viewed and/or clicked an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used for internal reporting and advertising optimisation only.
Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google Advertising Opt-out Page. Users may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics Opt-out Page. Users may opt out of third party vendor use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-out Page.
We use Hotjar in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimise this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users’ experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices. This includes a device’s IP address (processed during your session and stored in a de-identified form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), and the preferred language used to display our website. Hotjar stores this information on our behalf in a pseudonymized user profile. Hotjar is contractually forbidden to sell any of the data collected on our behalf. For further details, please see the ‘about Hotjar’ section of Hotjar’s support site.
Marketing purposes
When data is collected for marketing purposes we ensure the legitimate interests of our business do not override the interests or fundamental rights and freedoms’ of the individuals we are contacting. We work with accredited marketing agencies, and any information we collect ensures we can deliver targeted, relevant and timely marketing. We have contracts with these agencies which impose strict requirements to keep your information confidential and secure; your personal information will only be provided to us with your consent.
Marketing material and emails have unsubscribe options and contacts are able to opt out of communications if they choose.
Job applicants
Please read our GDPR Privacy Notice for Job Applicants by downloading it here.
Intellectual Property Rights
All intellectual property rights in or arising from this website, including all copyright belong to Simpson Associates unless otherwise stated. All rights are reserved.
Disclaimer
Simpson Associates makes every effort to ensure that the information on this website is accurate and up-to-date. We cannot, however, accept responsibility for any loss or inconvenience caused by reliance on inaccurate material contained in this site.
Links to other sites
Certain links, including hypertext links, in our site will take you to external websites. These are provided for your convenience and inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement or approval by Simpson Associates of the linked site, its operator or its content. We are not responsible for the content of any website outside of our site.
Accessibility
Simpson Associates endeavours at all times to make the site as accessible as reasonably possible to disabled users. In no way does Simpson Associates seek to deliberately discriminate against disabled users access to the website service in accordance with the Disability Discrimination Act 1995.
This privacy policy only covers this Simpson Associates website – websites linked to and from this site are not covered by this policy.
